<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Renzo Cammi</title>
    <link>https://rcammi.github.io/cammirenzo_portfolio/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Renzo Cammi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://rcammi.github.io/cammirenzo_portfolio/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Leed&#39;s United journey back to Premier League</title>
      <link>https://rcammi.github.io/cammirenzo_portfolio/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcammi.github.io/cammirenzo_portfolio/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>After 16 years Leed&amp;rsquo;s United returns to Premier League. Using data from FBref I was able to graph a simple line plot to show the long journey Leed&amp;rsquo;s had to take.
  Link to Github Repository</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Superliga season 2019/20 squads distribution of time played by age</title>
      <link>https://rcammi.github.io/cammirenzo_portfolio/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcammi.github.io/cammirenzo_portfolio/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>How playing time of players is distributed in Superliga Argentina squads. The teams are organized by their final position in the league. It also gives information about the average age of each team and how many points they were able to sum. The leagues average is 25.7 years old.
Althought, the league of Argentina has an export profile, most teams are able to hold to players in their prime (25.7 yrs old average age).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 defensive players of Superliga in season 2019/20</title>
      <link>https://rcammi.github.io/cammirenzo_portfolio/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcammi.github.io/cammirenzo_portfolio/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>Looking at the defensive facet of the game is not an easy approach using metrics. Firstly, teams that have more the ball will have less defensive actions per game, therefore all defensive metrics have toi be adjusted by the possession of the team. Seconldy, there aren&amp;rsquo;t many metrics at the moment that describe the way teams defend.
Its known that the best way to adjust defensive actions by possession is having the effective time possession of each team.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>